martinair.com 2014-04-23

# Martinair

### PRIVACY STATEMENT

This privacy statement covers the privacy policy of the Martinair website and the use of personal information as provided by you. The statement assumes the principle that you as the user have as much control as possible over your own privacy, and that Martinair will not, without your prior permission, make available any (personal) information – anything which would identify you as the user of the website – to any third parties.

**Processing of personal details  
** You may visit our website without telling us who you are and without having to provide us with any personal information.   

**IP Addresses/Cookies**  
Martinair’s web server automatically collects so-called ‘IP Addresses’. Your IP Address is a number by which other computers on the network can identify your computer, so that data (such as internet pages) can be sent to your computer. You cannot be personally identified with an IP Address.

A cookie is a compact piece of information that is saved onto your computer. During a visit to the Martinair website this cookie is turned on and consulted.

We use IP Addresses and cookies to analyse trends, to manage this website, to follow the use of the site (for example, the number of visitors to the site, busy and quiet periods) and to collect general demographical information.

Perhaps unnecessarily, these details are not connected to any personal information and cannot lead to establishing your identity.

**Links**  
This Martinair website contains links to other websites and/or sources. Martinair bears no responsibility or liability for any of these. This privacy statement has no bearing on any other websites or sources. We advise you to always read the privacy statements of other sites/sources carefully before you provide them with any of your personal details.

**Changes**  
This privacy statement is restricted to the use of, and possibilities on, this website. Any future changes or updates to this site could lead to changes in this privacy statement. It is therefore recommended to check this privacy statement regularly.

Finally, we shall use all information gathered via this site in accordance with this privacy statement and with the purpose for which the information was collected. If Martinair decides to use personally identifiable information in a manner that deviates from that specified in the privacy statement, Martinair will then inform the affected users of the site via email. The user shall then have the choice not to give his/her agreement for the information to be used in this manner.
